（特别行动组训练站 阿拉斯加）
《谍影重重4》
伦敦有个记者 叫西蒙·罗斯
There's a reporter in London named Simon Ross.
这我们拦截到一些不利于我们的电话记录 发现了他的名字
We caught some phone chatter we didn't like and his name came up.
他们已经派去一小队去那儿监视他
They put a team out there to take a better look.
一直在昼夜不停紧盯着他
They've been sitting on him pretty tight all day.
（马里兰州 贝塞斯达）
就在一小时前接到电话 我们有大麻烦了
I just got a call about an hour ago. We got a real problem here.
什么样的麻烦？
What kind of problem?
这个人是《卫报》的一名作者
This guy's a writer for The Guardian.
他正在准备一篇关于杰森·伯恩 绊脚石和黑石楠计划的报道
He's preparing an exposé on Jason Bourne, Treadstone and Blackbriar.
他怎么搞到的？
Sourced how?
不知道
Unknown.
从伯恩哪？怎么可能？
From Bourne? Is it possible?
你确信？
Possible?
我们6个星期前在莫斯科见过伯恩
We had Bourne six weeks ago in Moscow.
他带伤徒步 被一整编队伍追杀
He was on foot, wounded, with a full Cossack posse up his ass.
不知道他是怎么逃走的
Somehow, he walked out of there.
我现在对可能性没有概念了
I've kind of lost my perspective on what's possible.
你看起来很疲倦 艾斯拉
You sound tired, Ezra.
如果我是你至少会尝试着去处理
I would make more of an effort if I were you.
你好歹是美国中央情报局的局长
You're the director of the Central Intelligence Agency.
看在上帝的份上 那就表现得像样点
of the United States of America, for God's sake. Act like it.
如果我出处理这件事 马克 再出什么错
If I go down for this, Mark, if this goes any more wrong…
艾斯拉
Ezra,
老子给你配了一辆法拉利 你的人却像割草机一样对待
you were given a Ferrari and your people treated it like a lawn mower.
自己搞砸的事 自己擦屁股 这是常理
You break it, you bought it. It was ever thus.
呃 或许我该直接找瑞克·拜尔谈谈
Well, maybe I should be speaking directly to Ric Byer.
不用 你已经摊上够多麻烦了
No, no, no. You're in enough trouble already.
我会让他知道的
I'll let him know.
（弗吉尼亚州 雷斯顿）
（国家化验研究所 华盛顿）
朱莉 就这些了吗 好极了 多谢
Julie, is that the last of them? Terrific, thank you.
是绊脚石的最后命令？
So, the last audit on Treadstone?
嗯 第三页
Third page.
七周前了
Seven weeks ago.
这是中央情报局的还是我们的？
This is from the CIA, or this is ours?
不知道 他们的吧
Oh, no. It's theirs.
那一堆都是他们的
This whole pile is theirs.
有人在读战报吗？
Is anybody reading these ground cables?
我们得到了多少机密？
Look, how wide are we digging?
「得到多少」什意思？把所有的资料都给我拿来就是
What do you mean, "how wide?" Just get me everything.
绊脚石 黑石楠 成果拉斯等所有计划行动
Treadstone, Blackbriar, Outcome, LARX. All the beta programs.
所有都要带回翡翠湖
And that means take it all the way back to Emerald Lake.
我想要所有转换的要点 我想要所有人的研究结果
I want all points of convergence, I want all research personnel,
我想要知道任何人 任何时间
I want to know about anybody who talked.
谈论的任何东西
to anybody about anything at any time.
说真的 谁看过伯恩的资料？
Seriously, has anybody looked at this stuff on Bourne?
资料里所述简直不可思议
The field reports. It's incredible.
遗弃三年的计划还运作着 第一代实验对象 还在活动
Three years off-program, non-med, first-gen, still rolling.
我么能从中得到什么信息么？
If there's any way we can score some data off of this…
有人见他还活着么？
if they caught him alive…
我觉得他肯定有个基地
I mean, even as a base line.
不见得
Even forensically.
可能你参加错了会议
Maybe you're in the wrong meeting.
因为 我们现在的会议是关于传染病的
Because the meeting that we're having is about an infection.
我们在会议上讨论了一种严重的传染病
We're here talking about a serious infection.
所有人都想知道 它到底传播了多大范围
and all we're trying to do is determine how far it's spread.
目的是想知道 我们还要消磨多少耐心
so that we know how much we have to cut to save the patient.
你从没听过绊脚石？
You have never heard of Treadstone.
还有伯恩 我不管他们有没有把他装进袋子里扔到路边
And Bourne… I don't care if they bag him and drop the body on the sidewalk.
我们也不会去管这种事
We're not going to touch it.
现在把你的精力从那上面挪开
You're going to turn off that side of your head now.
和我们一起
and get with the rest of us here.
现在考虑的事的重要性不该放在这上面
And you're going to start to consider the magnitude of what we're facing.
如果危机波及到我们
if this moves sideways on us.
我们应该收集证据 在多挖掘点
Because if we get into this, we dig around,
找出那些CIA的蠢货留下的东西
and we find out these CIA clowns.
绊脚石搞砸了剩下的计划
have let this Treadstone mess metastasize into the rest of these programs?
希望 还没发生
Just pray that that doesn't happen.
（伦敦 滑铁卢车站）
我们刚从伦敦 滑铁卢火车站得到消息
We're just getting reports coming in now from Waterloo Station.
那发生一起枪击事件
that there has been a shooting.
跟我们一起去现场问下杰瑞米·汤普森
Let's take you live down there and speak to Jeremy Thompson.
杰瑞米
Jeremy?
滑铁卢车站仍旧一片骚乱
There's still an awful lot of confusion here at Waterloo Station.
如你所见 救护车就在现场
As you can see, ambulances have been called up.
死者是西蒙·罗斯 一名退伍的战地记者
The victim, Simon Ross, was a veteran reporter.
伦敦卫报报导
with The Guardian newspaper in London.
受害者被宣告当场死亡
He was pronounced dead at the scene.
警方告知我们
Police are now telling us there was at least one,
至少有一个或许三个人开枪
and possibly as many as three, shots fired.
西蒙·罗斯 一名卫报的记者
Simon Ross, a reporter with The Guardian newspaper…
- 嗨 詹姆士 - 嗨
- Hey, James.- Hey.
哦 不好意思 我不知道我正往回走
Oh, shit, sorry. I didn't know I was coming back.
没事儿
It's all right.
告诉希尔科特博士我在这
Can you tell Dr. Hillcott I'm here?
好的
You got it.
（斯特森·莫兰塔公司）
明天见
See you tomorrow.
我不知道他进来了
I had no idea he was coming in.
- 他是6号 - 是第6号？
- It's Number Six. - Number Six?
七月之后我们就没见过他了
We haven't seen him since July.
呃 好的
Mmm-hmm. Okay.
需要建立新的基本数据 胆碱和神经传导数据
"Need new base panels, choline profile, nerve conduction."
我想要进行完整地移植诊断
I want a full engraftment workup.
我会联系国家分析小组 确认是否能被授权
I'm gonna call NRAG and see if we can't get approval to put him under.
我想要抽取他的骨髓和完整的脊髓
I want a marrow and a full spinal while we have him.
好的
Okay.
他怎么样了？
How is he?
差不多废了
He's prepped.
他等着的时候记得让他喝点水
He drank a half-liter of water while he was waiting.
去年他肾脏出过问题
He had some renal issues last year.
恩 可能他渴了吧
Or maybe he was thirsty.
我请求再化验一下
I have a pending task request.
知道 我看过了
I know, I read it.
确保我完成了皮质研究
I'm trying to complete my cortex study.
对比静脉注射 他能保持更加稳定
He'll get a more sustained contrast off an IV.
不同意？
I'm approved?
额
Mmm-hmm.
太感谢了
Yes! Thank you!
抱歉 让你久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
有段时间没见你了
We haven't seen you in awhile.
所以得让你做个全面检查
so we're going to be doing a full spec workup.
三个月前刚做过了
I just had a full spec three months ago.
是的 我们修改了时间表
Yeah, well, we had to change the boundary schedules.
而就新标准而言 你已经迟了一个礼拜
and you're a week over the new line.
直说吧 我要是10天前早来
Let me get this straight, if I had come in.
是不是什么事都没有？
10 days ago, I would have been in the clear?
是不是就不会这样拖时间？
It never gets any longer, does it?
你得把那个摘掉
You're gonna have to take that off.
今天 我很荣幸向大家介绍一人
Today, I have the honor of introducing the man.
他将介绍我们的贵宾
who is going to introduce our guest of honor.
伯特 这是阿尔伯特·赫希博士
Bert? Doctor Albert Hirsch.
我初遇丹·希尔科特是在1987年
I first met Dan Hillcott in 1987…
在一场绝对是有史以来
at what must have been the most boring.
最无聊的神经心理学研讨会上
neuropsych conference ever held.
我们离开了那无聊的会议
We managed to escape that dreary ballroom.
找个黑暗的角落喝了一杯
and find a dark corner and a cold beverage.
此后 我们乐此不彼
And we've been finding dark corners ever since.
哦 真逗
My God.
你在哪找到这个的
Where did you find this?
Youtube上
YouTube.
我以为每件事都做的很保密呢
I thought we had everything firewalled.
我觉得也应该是
Yeah, so did I.
我仍旧觉得CIA会插手绊脚石
But then again, I thought the CIA would handle Treadstone,
所以我觉得我在兜圈子
so maybe I'm just behind the curve.
呃
Hmm.
你就知道这些吗？
Well, is that it? Is that all of it?
当然不是 显然他们认为
No, no. They apparently thought it was Okay.
六个东西联系在一起是正确的
to attend about a half a dozen of these things together.
又能证明什么？
Proving what?
我们正在监视绊脚石的医药部主管和他们的成果计划
We're looking at the medical directors of Treadstone and Outcome.
公开庆祝他们的成果
publicly celebrating their top secret man-crush.
如果伯恩的肮脏事让绊脚石暴漏 他们会把 赫希赶出去
If this Bourne mess exposes Treadstone, they will turn Hirsch inside out.
他们会一直告诉希尔科特直到我们了解情况
They'll be talking to Hillcott before we even know what happened.
有什么损失？
What's the damage?
收割计划吧 我丢掉收割计划
Outcome. We'd lose Outcome.
什么意思？
Uh, meaning what?
意味着我们将会失去计划
Meaning we will burn the program to the ground.
我的意思是陷入谷底
And I mean from top to bottom.
就因为这个？
Because of this?
因为他们是朋友？
Because they're friends?
那两个家伙是我们的顶头上司啊
These two guys built our platform!
你想在CNN上看到这个吗？
You want to wake up and see this on CNN?
天啊 瑞克 这算什么事啊
Jesus, Ric. Just like that?
赫希 和 希尔科特
Hirsch and Hillcott?
太多人认识他们了
How many people even understand this work,
别管他们让他们被抓好了
let alone have the will to pursue it?
不是还没到这一步吗？
Nothing has even happened yet!
我们必须先做准备
And we have to get ready.
准备什么？
Ready for what?
我们并没有失去全部 手里还有技术 数据
We don't lose it all, we've got the science. We'll keep the data.
我们J组人联系还是安全的
All of our JSOK liaisons seem to be safe.
把b计划隐秘起来
We've got the beta programs tucked away.
假装重新开始
We'll take a pause, and we'll rebuild it.
我也希望有更好的选择 可是
I wish there was a better alternative, but…
天哪
God.
你想包庇让我藏你这？
Are you going to pretend you don't know I'm here?
礼貌而已
I was just trying to be polite.
我不想那么快见到你
I wasn't expecting you so soon.
你来做什么？搜山？
What did you do? Did you come over the mountain?
你一直跟踪我？
Don't they forward my position?
你拿着那录音两天了
You beat the record by two days.
- 是吗？- 是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
你不知道那有一盘录音？
You didn't know there was a record?
不知道 从不知道
No. It never came up.
不是你的录音对吧？
It wasn't your record, was it?
没人来过这儿的山
No one comes over the mountain.
是的 就我一个
Yeah, well, I did.
顺便告诉你 我是亚伦
I'm Aaron, by the way.
你为什么那么做？
Why did you do that?
没日没夜的 为什么冒这个险？
If you weren't on the clock, why take the risk?
来这山上干什么？
Why take the mountain?
我丢掉了我的药
I lost my chems.
我丢了所有东西 这就是原因
I dropped my program kit, that's why.
哦
All right.
原谅我叫你回来
Protocol is for me to call in your arrival.
他们想要那些重要的东西 你杀光他们了？
They're going to want a sample pick-up. You got blood work, right?
今天 算我欠你的
I owe today.
好 现在拉过来
All right, pull it now.
那些家伙花了三个小时到这
The drone takes about three hours to get up here.
我弄了点吃的 屎都风干了
so I'll get some food started. You can dry your shit.
听着
So, look…
我真遇到麻烦了
I got a real problem, here.
我来这因为我丢了我的药
I came over that mountain because I lost my chems.
说什么呢？
What are you taking?
每天？都吃半颗绿色的
My daily? Phys meds, 250 green.
一颗蓝色的
Cognitive programs, 400 blue.
但是丢了
Define "lost."
丢了 爬到20米高的悬崖上时
Lost. Fell into the rocks off a 20-meter cliff.
丢了
Lost.
怎么回事？
How is that possible?
听着 我离开休息站之
Look, I've had a pack of wolves.
后就有一群狼追着我 知道不？
on my ass since I left the drop, Okay?
我还以为我甩掉了它们 它们在河边追上了我
I thought I lost them, but they came at me at the river,
我只好飞檐走壁爬去了山谷 我想在夜晚集合
so I took the ledge up to the ravine to try to rally out the night.
但是我错了
I chose wrong.
我在野外被捉住了 爬山不能
I got caught out in the open, I couldn't climb.
生火不能 我的双手都僵硬了
I couldn't make a fire, my hands got stiff.
所以我扔下了货
I dropped them.
你得在报告中把这些写下来
You're going to have to write that up.
嗯 那个是你的么？
So, is that yours?
啥？
Hmm?
那血腥的活儿
The blood work?
是你的 对吧？
That's yours, isn't it?
你不是联系人 对吧？
You're not a contact, are you?
听着 很抱歉我那样叫你
Look, I'm sorry to call you out like that.
只是
It's just that…
我之前从未见过计划里的任何人
I have never met anybody in the program before.
从来没有过 任何人 你就像是第一
Never, nobody. You're the…
我知道你这儿有一些多余的药
I know you have some extra chems here.
那我应该给你定量分配直到明天么？
I'm not supposed to ration you out until you leave tomorrow.
是的
Yeah.
你今天吃药了没？
Did you chem today?
只吃了绿色的
Green only.
我32小时没用蓝药了
I haven't had a blue in 32 hours.
（中情局潜伏机构 反恐局 纽约市）
各位 听清楚了
People, listen up.
马上有一个威胁
We have an imminent threat.
这里是美国安全紧急5级事件
This is a national security emergency, priority level five.
是威利斯
It's Wills.
瑞克·拜尔
Ric Byer.
嘿 嗯 他来了
Hey. Uh, he's here.
伯恩就在 纽约
Bourne is here, in New York.
什么？
What?
杰森·伯恩在曼哈顿
Jason Bourne is in Manhattan.
确认
Confirmed.
他还活着还能动 我就知道这些 我得挂了
He's alive and mobile. That's all I have. I gotta go.
你的朋友们来了
Your friends are here.
我知道
I know.
你不觉得很奇怪么？
Don't you think that's strange?
那些狼 它们不会这么做
The wolves? They don't do that.
它们不会跟踪人类
They don't track people.
是的
Yeah.
也许它们不觉得你是人类
Maybe they don't think you're human.
有多少我们的人在那儿？
So, how many of us are there?
你问的太多了
You ask too many questions.
也许他们也不知道
Maybe you don't know, either.
那你在这儿是做什么的？
So, what are you doing up here anyway?
你怎么知道我不是在评估你呢？
How do you know that I'm not evaluating you?
噢 我不知道 你是么？
I don't know. Are you?
也许我根本就不在乎
Maybe I don't care.
你曾经在乎过什么？
Do you ever not care?
也许是你在评估我
Maybe you're evaluating me.
我销声匿迹了4天 所以我才到这儿来
I went off the grid for four days, that's why I'm here.
只是常规检查
I skipped my check-in.
现在我却在这个破烂的蛮荒之地
Now I'm on this bullshit scavenger hunt.
好笨 他们有他们的理由
They have their reasons.
是的 好吧
Yeah, well…
我的手腕和大腿疼痛才是有理由的 但是我也不是很确定
I thought I was having my wrist slapped, but now I'm not so sure.
我还是在努力猜测
I'm still trying to figure out if you're.
你到底是想杀了我 还是想给我一个激励的谈话
supposed to kill me or give me a pep talk.
说真的 你想太多了
Seriously, man, you think too much.
我们这不是在互相说说么？
Aren't we wired to stick our nose in, you and I?
300英里之外才有另外一个人
There's not another person for 300 miles.
这附近没人在偷听 拜托 你必须得给我个话题
I know nobody's listening. Come on, you've got to give me something.
来聊聊
Talk to me, come on!
为什么他们把你扔在地里然后不管你了？
Why did they pull you off the field and put you up here?
这不是什么体能训练 是吧？
It's not physical, with the way you've been moving, so what did you do?
降低任务？开始为你着想？
Turn down an assignment? Start thinking for yourself?
谈恋爱了？
Fall in love?
你恋爱了
You fell in love.
拿着这个防止狼来
It's better for wolves.
门那边儿有着个双层弹药 需要多少你就拿多少
There's an ammo box by the door, you take as much as you need.
我们的谈话结束了
We're done talking.
狼来了 等着 提前开枪 就能打中了
You ate, you're pulling out early. You should hit it.
好的
Okay.
- 改天再聊？- 好的
- Some othertime, then. - Yeah.
- 谢谢 - 祝你好运
- Thanks. - Good luck.
（杰森·伯恩）
（韩国 首尔）
这是什么？
What's this?
丹 我觉得我们需要确认一些事情
I think that we need to clarify something here, Don.
确认什么？
Clarify what?
你不停的说什么不可接受
You keep using the word "unacceptable"…
我不要知道你这么说到底是什么意思
and I want to know exactly what you think you mean by that.
不可接受就是不可接受的意思
"Unacceptable" means exactly that.
我不喜欢你告诉我的这些
I don't like what you're telling me,
我也不喜欢你说话的方式
I don't like how you're telling me.
瑞克 我们处于情报局出境任务中的一个关键时期
We're in a critical phase on four missions, Ric.
如果我们现在停止 损失将不可估量
The intelligence loss, if we stop now, it couldn't be quantified.
不 可以估量
Yes, actually, it could.
你会回到我们开始计划之前的状态
You'd be right back to where you were before we delivered the program.
别告诉我是结果有问题
Don't tell me there's a problem with Outcome.
因为如果那样我早就知道了
because I'd be hearing about it.
- 我可没说是的 - 你什么都没说
- I didn't say there was. - You're not saying much of anything.
一周一片
One pill, once a week.
每8天一次
Every eight days.
没有蓝药和绿药了？
So, no more blues and greens.
我们正在过渡计划里的所有人
We're transitioning everyone in the program.
你还记得如何保持节食计划的方法吧？
Do you remember how to keep an accurate diet log?
是的
Yes.
你到底懂不懂第四号任务的程序？
Do you understand their full utility?
我们刚刚将伊朗导弹计划推迟了36个月
We just set Iran's missile program back.
我们在一名潜伏特工的帮助下
36 months with one deep-cover agent.
最近2年里最好的侦查成果
The best action recon out of North Korea.
也是计划的特工执行的
in the last two years came from Outcome.
- 我完全知道这些 - 你知道我们等待得到
- I'm fully aware of this. - Do you know how long we've waited.
一个来自巴基斯坦三军情报局内部的行动需要多久么？
to get a real, long-term operative inside Pakistani ISI?
你这是叫我清理掉
You're asking me to wipe the most valuable.
以前收集起来用过的 最有价值的资产
intel-gathering assets we've ever put in the field.
我们在快速停止这个计划
We're shutting things down immediately.
这个偶然事件会被掩盖的完美无缺
and this contingency was covered loud and clear.
告诉我这可不是我们交流的方式
Tell me this isn't why we're having this conversation.
杰森·伯恩逃跑了 对不？
Jason Bourne got away, didn't he?
这才是根本原因 是不是？
That's what this is all about, isn't it?
我可以看见这计划里所有的行动 除了你的
I have visibility on every action program in the system except yours.
我很痛恨听到我不能做这件事 不能看那件事的各种理由
I'm sick of hearing the reason I can't do something or see something.
只因为我没有得到国家研究资产的许可
is because it hasn't cleared the National Research Assay Group.
你是怎么搞定这种事情的？
Where do you pull this kind of weight?
丹 我很爱国 和你一样
Don, I'm a patriot, the same as you are.
我为国家流过血 就像你一样
I bleed over this the same way you do.
但你和我有工作
But you and I have our jobs.
因为我们有能力去做必须做的事情
because we've got the strength to do what's necessary.
我很抱歉 但是现在就是这样
and I'm sorry, but right now, this is it.
外面跟回到凡间一样 真不爽
It's really coming down out there. It's getting ugly.
哦 是么？
Oh. yeah?
多谢你的提醒 不想再超人一步了？
Well, maybe I should try to get ahead of it, huh?
不 太晚了 我只能逗留在此
No, it's too late for that. Just stick around.
我对侦查这片地区需要一些帮助
I need some help squaring the place away, anyway.
是么 我啥也不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
我甚至还需要为此开点药
I already have to do that medication write-up.
我都不知道我是否还会解释
I don't know if I want to have to explain.
我行程的一切 你懂么
my itinerary as well, you know what I mean?
别担心那些药 我搞定了
Don't worry about the chems, I got that covered.
我需要去看一眼
I'm gonna have a look.
你听见了？
Are you hearing that?
你在等着什么么？
Are you expecting anything?
这种天气 没一个提示？
In this weather, without a heads-up?
肯定在靠近
Well, it's definitely getting closer.
接通了么
What do you got?
没有 什么也没有
Nothing, man, I got nothing.
- 那东西没坏吧 - 没坏
- Is it working? - Yeah, it's working.
设备没问题
The gear is fine. It's not the gear.
好吧 也许是补给小组来了
Well, maybe it's a resupply.
他们昨天来过了 怎么都没办法着陆
They were here yesterday, and they can't land in this, anyway.
这到底是什么？
Who the hell is it?
不知道
I don't know.
不知道 我们该分头行动去找找
I don't know. We should spread.
- 好的 - 我去查查大本营那里
- Yeah. - Look, I'll take the nest.
- 有消息了让我知道 好不？- 好的
- Let me know when you get eyes on it, Okay? - Yeah.
国防情报 特别行动 无人机指挥中心
她要在这清除我们？
Is she gonna clear us here?
我得趁早解决这事儿 以免变得更糟糕
I'd like to get above this before it gets any sloppier.
坚持住 刚刚过去了
Now, hold on. Just, there's a…
收到 单机 我也看见了 两分钟后到那儿
Copy, Solo, I saw it, too. Give us a minute.
怎么回事？等等 等等
What's the issue? Hang on, hang on.
收到 单机 正在查找资源
Roger, Solo. Sourcing now.
好像那儿还有一个活动的信号
It looks like there's still an active signal back there.
什么意思？
Excuse me?
- 是你那边还是我 - 是我这边
- Is that on your end or is that… - My end.
我们很难进行信号交换
We're having a hard time getting a handshake.
收到 单机保持通话
Roger, Solo. Holding on relay.
我以为你连上他了
I thought you had them linked.
我们连上了
We did.
目标已经瞄准 精确到结构
They were lined up, all the way to the structure.
两个目标一直都是绿色的
Both targets were green, all the way in.
- 确认ID - 不知道
- Is there a PID? - Unknown.
- 敌人？- 不知道
- Hostile? - Unknown.
这不是卫星回音吧？
It's not a satellite echo, is it?
不是的 长官
No, sir.
她在干嘛？
What's she doing?
再往回退
She's playing it back.
该死的冬天 我们得回头去了从头再来么？
I don't want to wait on her. We're going to have to come around.
距离燃料极限还有多久？
How far are you from bingo fuel?
还有20分钟
Twenty minutes on station.
最好赶得上
Better get on it.
确认 单机 我们还需要一次通过许可
Affirmative, Solo, but we're gonna need another pass here.
她知道我们啥也看不见 是吧？发射
She knows we can't see shit, right? Check it.
收到 新弹上膛
Roger that. New profile engaged.
我们现在就来
We're coming around now.
单机收到 东南 东
Roger that, Solo. East-southeast.
直奔山谷
Coming right back up the valley.
请求报告燃料状况
Requesting fuel graph, say your state.
状态30加2
State two-plus-SO to splash.
受到 单机 燃料情况正常
Copy, Solo. Fuel to bingo is green.
现在查找目标信号
Sourcing target beacon now.
不是吧
What just happened?
消失了 他去哪儿了？
It's gone. Where the hell did it go?
你说他去哪儿了 是什么意思？
What do you mean, "Where did it go?"
单机 我们 我们找不到那个信号了
Solo, we are negative on that signal here.
我们失去了第二个信号
We just lost that second beacon.
找不到 单机 找不到 所有的探测器和系统都是正常的
Negative, negative, Solo. All sensors and systems are green.
诊断系统绿色 飞机正常
Diagnostics are green, aircraft is green.
所有都是好的 就是找不到目标
I got everything but a target here.
不是系统的问题 探测器是好的
It is not a system issue. Sensors are good.
我换到红外辐射再试试看
All right, we're going to switch to IR and take a look.
- 收到 - 换到热辐射
- Roger. - Switching to thermal.
单机 我需要你最后一次确认
Solo, can I get your last confirmed…
这是咋回事？
What the hell was that?
红冠 我们遇到了点情况
Red Crown, we're getting some music.
你撞到了什么东西？
You hit something.
我不是那么想的 红冠 你看见了吗？
I don't think so. Red Crown, you getting this?
是的 什么都没有
There is nothing there. There is nothing.
这到底是怎么回事？
What the hell is going on, here?
说不是坠落 那是说被击毁了 他们确定么？
It didn't just go down, it was shot down? They're sure about that?
他们这样告诉我的
That's what I was told.
谁干的？用什么武器？
By who? With what?
他们不知道
They don't know.
当时他们在追踪另一个信号
They were sourcing a second signal when it happened.
不 那时我们来不及了 我要叫人来清理这些了
No, no, no, we didn't have time. I'm calling for clearance now.
肯定会有人在大门等着我们
There's got to be someone meeting us at the gate.
无人驾驶飞机准备好了吗？
They have a drone ready?
有一架正在加油呢
They're fueling one now.
他们确定了信号
They parsed the signal.
是亚伦·克劳斯
It's Aaron Cross.
靠
Shit.
准备好了 长官
You're all set, sir.
接近方位角 距之前的方位30°
Let's approach off azimuth, 30 degrees off our last pass.
很好
Good for me.
红冠收到 方位30° 3-0-0
Red Crown to contact. Three-zero-zero for 30.
好了 看到信号了
There you are. There's my signal.
收到信号 单机
Signal is hot, Solo.
信号很活跃 现在好了
Signal is up and live. And here we go.
刚才怎么没有？
Where's that been?
无所谓 反正现在是我的了
Doesn't matter now. It's mine.
收到 单机 信号很强
Copy, Solo. Strong signal.
这家伙用的是什么武器？
What kind of weapon system is this guy operating?
可能有来福枪
He's probably got a rifle.
那也是一高火力的来福
It's a high-powered rifle.
我们有多少时间？
What's our time frame, here?
15分钟左右
Fifteen minutes, plus or minus.
我正在试着重新储备
Just trying to factor the storm.
单机 目标静止 启动激光制导
Roger, Solo. Target is static. Engaging laser now.
嘿
Hey!
离开这
Get out of here!
快点
Go on, get out of here!
走开
Get out!
激光已启动
Laser armed.
感应器和温度已确认
Sensor and thermal confirmed.
- 还有多久？- 30秒
- Where are we? - Thirty seconds.
你应该离我远点的
You should have left me alone.
装配导弹
Arming missile.
发射导弹
Missile away.
他在移动了
There he goes, he's moving now.
一会就不动了
Not for long.
目标击毁
Target destroyed.
收到 确认攻击 目标击毁
Copy, Solo. Kill confirmed, target destroyed.
看起来不错嘛
Looking good?
看起来 不错
Looks good. Looks cold and clear.
长官恕我直言 现在不是那个时候
With all due respect, sir, now is not the best time.
20分钟内这个地方就会毁了
In 20 minutes, this place is going to fall apart.
我知道 我愿意冒这个险 我们需要谈谈
I'm aware of that, I'll take the chance. We need to talk.
停止你现在在做的 回头是岸
I need you to stop what you're doing and turn around.
这是命令
That's an order.
我们被内线坑了 行了吧？
We got screwed on the intel, Okay?
没人知道那里还有人呢
Nobody knew those people were in there.
对于我们要求你做的工作
It would be perfectly normal for a person to have doubts.
有不道德的怀疑是十分正常的
about the morality of what we just asked you to do.
这是个问题吗 长官？
Is that a question, sir?
不是 听好我要告诉你的话
No, it's not. Tune in to what I'm trying to say to you.
你知道是什么吗？食恶使者是什么？
Do you know what a sin-eater is?
那是我们 我们是食恶使者
That's what we are. We are the sin-eaters.
意味着在这种关系中 我们把道德底线拿出来
It means that we take the moral excrement that we find in this equation.
并且深埋在内心里
and we bury it down deep inside of us.
这样其他的损失 可以让我们独善其身
so that the rest of our cause can stay pure.
这是我们的工作
That is the job.
在道德上我们没法自我辩解 但是绝对必须的
We are morally indefensible and absolutely necessary.
你明白了吗？
Do you understand?
完事了？
Will that be all?
把伤口处理了
Stitch that up.
6小时后飞机上见
I'm gonna put you on a plane to Yemen in six hours.
我会准备好的
I'll be ready.
我早告诉你她会朝我们来的
I told you she'd be coming at us.
恩 我知道 你需要保持冷静 特里
Yeah, I need you to stay calm, Terry, Okay?
你就要进行参议院听证会了
They're giving her a Senate hearing.
你咋能不觉得这是个问题呢？
How can you not see that as a problem?
她知道伯恩 她知道黑石楠行动 她还知道 赫希
She knows Bourne, she knows Blackbriar, she knows Hirsch.
她知道他妈的整个行动
She's got a handle on the whole goddamn operation.
我真不明白你咋能保持这么冷静的
I don't see how the hell you could be so calm about this!
呃 她能说啥？
Well, what can she say?
她能说啥？
What can she say?
如果她从那里出去了 然后告诉他们
What if she gets up there and she says,
绊脚石和黑石楠计划 你就觉得那就完了？
"Treadstone, Blackbriar, you think that was it?"
你以为杰森·伯恩是所有的秘密？
"You think that Jason Bourne was the whole story?"
抱歉 但还有很多其他的
"Sorry, there's a lot more going on here."
如果她告诉他们绊脚石只是冰山一角怎么办？
What if she tells them that Treadstone was just the tip of the iceberg?
你看 你要是非要紧张
Look, you want to sweat something?
那就担心收获计划吧 因为我们还在森林里呢
Worry about Outcome, because we're still not out of the woods.
但是关于别的项目 她知道的没那么多
But as far as our other programs, she doesn't know that much.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
因为我们在监视她的一言一行
Because we're tapped into everything she says and does.
啥？
What?
电话 邮件 车 房子 律师
Phones, email, cars, house, lawyer.
她搭上杰森·伯恩的时候开始就已经被我们掌握了
She was cooked the minute she hitched her wagon to Jason Bourne.
她协助并怂恿了一个国际逃犯
She aided and abetted an international fugitive.
她阻止了我们停止一个流氓组织的行动
She prevented the agency from shutting down a rogue operation.
她违背了所有誓言准则和条例
She violated every oath and code of conduct that matters.
然后 是她把那个混蛋带进了美国
For Christ's sake, she brought the son of a bitch back to America.
谁知道她的动机是什么
Now, God knows what her motives are,
但 很明显 保护这个国家不是其中一个
but it's clear that protecting this country is not one of them.
这要搁以前就是叛国了
That used to be called treason.
配平方程式 然后应该得出一个常量
Even the solution here. Now, that should be coming up as a constant.
你在这呢啊 我不明白这些数据的意义
There you are. I don't understand these values…
天啊 不要啊
My God, no!
- 你听见那个了吗？- 听见了
- Did you hear that? - Yeah.
那是什么？
What is that?
就是枪响
It's a gun.
- 不 不 不 - 不 是枪响
- No. I… - No. Yeah. No, it was gunfire.
不 求你了 不 不
No, please. No, no, no!
救命
Help!
开门 他在向我们开枪 放我出去
Open the door! He's shooting us! Open the door!
开门 他有枪
Open the door! He's got a gun!
开门
Open the door!
救命
Help!
我的天
Oh, my God.
我们光看着门管啥用？赶紧跑吧
We got to be able to get a card!
我们必须进去
We have to be able to get in there!
- 怎么拉？- 我们必须到后门去
- What's happening? - We gotta go for the back door.
锁了 他可能把门锁了
It's locked. He locked the back door.
不 求你了
No, please.
他会杀光我们的
He's gonna kill us all.
不要那样 我的天
Don't do this. Oh, my God.
走开
Move!
他在里面到处开枪
He's shooting everyone in there!
我需要通行卡 谁有？
I need a red lab access card! Who's got a red lab access card?
他们从楼上带着一个下来
They're bringing one down from upstairs.
他们都在里面 有卡的都在里面
They're all in there. Everyone who has one is in there.
拉里 你在哪呢？ 我需要紧急卡 现在
Billy, where are you, man? I need a red card now!
你在干什么？
Don… What are you doing?
靠 他把门把手卸了
Shit, the handle's off.
你看 门把手掉了
The handle's off!
站住 放下武器
Drop it! Stop! Drop the weapon!
把枪放下 放下武器
Drop it! Drop the weapon!
调查人员仍在寻找这次
Investigators are still searching for some explanation.
工作场合谋杀事件背后的原因
behind the workplace murder-suicide.
只留下又一个美国群体在震惊 哀痛中
that left another American community grieving and shocked.
当地警察和联邦官员
Police and federal authorities.
在全面调查实验室的设施
were poring over the lab facility…
他们需要见你 马上
The boys need to see you right away.
需要让他们马上离开那
Let's get that Foite story out there right away.
我会处理的
I'll take care of it.
（度戒严实验室内发生谋杀案 嫌犯杀害五名同事）
那后面的这块区域呢？
And this area, back here?
已经都用作仓库了
That's all been converted to storage.
邮件发来的蓝图上不是仓库
Because it says on the blueprint, and even on the board, there,
而是一个医学实验机构
that it's a medical examination suite.
我是说 这是哪种实验？
I mean, what kind of examinations are we talking about?
好了 让我看下手
There we go. May I see the hand, please?
恩 愈合的不错
Oh, that has healed well.
有感觉减退的症状吗？
Any diminished sensation?
没有
Nope.
你要把我放倒吗 医生？
Are you trying to put me down, doc?
恐怕你送来的
I'm afraid there's been a few gaps.
样本有点问题 所以
in your sample deliveries, so…
我们需要再次确认
…we need a full work-up this visit.
又来一个？
Another one?
为啥？因为我丢了一滴血？
Why? Is it 'cause I missed a blood drop?
那么 你觉得这管用吗 医生？
So, how do you think it works, doc?
这些药 我们就叫暂停
That we can just call a timeout?
你取样的时候 世界都静止了
Everything stops while you pull your samples?
那你为什么不躺下来 放松
Why don't you lie down and relax?
好的
Yeah.
你觉得我们做的事怎么样？
What do you think that we do out there?
好了 信息够多了
Okay, that's enough information.
不 我
No, I…
算了 你就是一个医生
Well, you're just a doctor.
你知道我们被监视着呢吧？
You know we're on camera.
真的？
Really?
所以你特意打扮了？
Is that why you make such an attractive appearance?
好了 现在请从100倒数
Okay, why don't you count backward from 100, please?
（芝加哥）
（马里兰州实验室枪击案 六人死亡）
喂？
Hello?
是的 大门应该是开着的
Yeah, the gate should be open.
然后左转 大概半英里远
Bear to the left. It's about half-a-mile up.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 希林博士？ - 嗯哼
- Dr. Shearing? - Uh-huh.
嘿 我是康妮·多德博士
Hi, I'm Dr. Connie Dowd.
- 嘿 还好吧？- 挺好的 谢谢
- Hi, how are you? - Well, thanks.
这是特工拉里·胡珀
This is Special Agent Larry Hooper.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
请进
Please. Come in.
谢谢您让我过来
Thanks for letting us come out.
房子真漂亮 大工程
It's a remarkable property. What a project.
是啊 我实在不想讨论这房子
Yeah, I really don't want to talk about the house.
除非你想买下来
Not unless you want to buy it.
啊 请坐吧 我想
Sit, I guess. Please.
就告诉你一声 行吧
Just so you know, Okay,
直到1小时前 我完全不知道有这次见面
I didn't know anything about this meeting until an hour ago.
昨天晚上也没人说过
And nobody last night said to make time.
「约个时间或挤出时间来」这样的话
or pick a time, or anything like that.
然后今天早上我买张飞机票去看我妹妹
And then, this morning, I buy a plane ticket to see my sister.
突然周围就4级戒备状态了
and suddenly it's like DEFCON 4 around here.
这不是妄想好不？
And that is not paranoia, Okay?
这基本就冲我面来的
That is pretty much directly in my face!
我理解
Understood.
我们难道应该忽略你吗？
Should we not be paying attention?
你能让我们俩单独待会吗 拉里？
Can you leave us alone, Larry?
你看
Look.
你刚刚经历了及其惊骇的事情
You've just been through an extremely traumatic experience.
是的 你是学的什么 博士？
Yeah. Doctor of what?
你是谁？
What are you?
临床心理学
Clinical psychology.
哦 那你做什么
Oh. So, what do you do?
给间谍提供悲伤辅导？
You give grief counseling to spies?
你的安全级别很高 玛塔
You have a very unusual security clearance, Marta.
你应该能想到 买张机票
You should expect that buying a ticket.
去蒙特利尔 并且不告诉任何人会引起一些警惕
to Montreal without telling anyone would set off some bells.
对 那我也有我自己的警惕 是把？
Yeah, I've got some bells of my own going off, Okay?
我是说 你是打算告诉
I mean, are you going to be the person who tells me.
我到底发生了什么
what the hell is going on here,
还是你也是一神秘的保姆？
or are you just the next mystery babysitter?
你觉得发生了什么？
What do you think is going on?
我现在要尝试不思考
What I'm trying to do is not think.
我只想停止思考
I just… I want to stop thinking.
这种感觉你跟别人说过吗？
Have you discussed those feelings with anyone else?
妹妹 朋友？
Your sister? Friends?
你说真的？
Are you for real?
彼得·博伊德呢？
What about Peter Boyd?
哇
Wow.
好吧
Okay.
那我们什么都能说是吧？没底线？
So, we're into everything, is that it? Is anything off-limits here?
你读过你的就业保密合同吗？
Have you ever read your employment security contract?
我读过我
Have I read my…
如果你再问我明不明白限制泄密的内容
If you're asking me whether I understand my disclosure restrictions,
是的 我有生化和
yes, I have a PhD in biochemistry.
基因病毒学的博士后奖学金
with postdoctoral fellowships in virology and genetics.
我知道怎么阅读
I know how to read!
我不明白的是 为什么我的同事
What I don't understand is why my colleague.
突然发精神病然后杀了实验室所有的人
has a psychotic episode and shot everyone in the lab.
你知道我们在那干什么吗？
Are you aware of what we do in there?
你知道吗？
Are you?
我是说 我怎么知道你甚至明白这次谈话
I mean, how do I know that you're even cleared for this conversation?
你有没有讨论过这次事件吗？
Have you discussed anything to do with the incident.
跟任何人 除了调查员？
with anyone other than the investigators?
彼得·博伊德 8个月前就搬出去了
Peter Boyd moved out eight months ago.
哦但我猜你已经知道了
But I guess you already know that.
不 我没有跟他谈过
And, no, I haven't spoken to him.
你说你和佛洛德博士除了工作外没有任何关系？
You stated that you and Dr. Foite had no relationship outside of work.
没有
None.
他公寓里有些东西
There was material in his apartment that indicates he had.
表明他跟你有不寻常的关系
an unusual fixation with you.
照片 日记 他们还找到几件衣服
Photographs, journal entries. They found several articles of clothing.
什… 什么
What?
你跟他曾有过任何形式的冲突吗？
Did you ever rebuff him in any way?
没有
No.
没 我
No, no, I…
我一直以为他是同性恋
I always thought he was gay.
你看 没人暗示你应该为这次事件负责
Look, no one is suggesting that you're responsible for what happened.
哇哦 多谢啊
Oh. Thank you.
存活者往往会感到愧疚
Survivors often experience feelings of guilt.
这些感觉会被放大
Those feelings can be amplified.
他让你活下来的事实
by the realization that he let you live.
他让我活下来？
That he let me live?
你看到那个视频了吗？
Have you seen the video?
你真觉得那是事实？
Do you really think that's what it shows?
你问的问题都是错的
You are asking all the wrong questions!
我应该问什么 玛塔？
What should I be asking, Marta?
有人看过弗洛德博士的血液结果吗？
Has anyone looked at Dr. Foite's blood work?
看过吗？
Have they?
我是说 那是唯一可以解释的地方
I mean, that is the only thing that is going to make any sense, here.
他的行为
His behavior was…
你看 斯特森有一些项目
Look, there are projects at Sterisyn,
国家防御项目 可以解释为什么他做出这样的事
defense projects that could explain why he did what he did.
那里的人在研究行为控制
And people there are working on behavioral design.
是一种程序化的神经行为控制
It's programmable behavior, neural design.
你 你明白我告诉你的吗？
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
我认为他受到了实验室某种东西的影响
I think he was exposed to something at the lab.
找到了
Found it.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
那是我的枪 这他妈的是什么？
That's my gun. What the hell is this?
你有潜在自杀危险
You're a potential suicide risk.
不 等会 你怎么
No. Wait a minute. How did you…
- 他怎么找到的？ - 玛塔
- How did he find that? - Marta…
不 不 行了 这次谈话结束了
No, no. Okay. This meeting is now over.
- 你俩出去 现在 - 玛塔
- I want you both out of here, right now! - Marta…
不 他在我房子里乱翻
No! He has been snooping around my house!
玛塔 我想让你离开这
Marta, I want to sign off here today!
我想让你上那架飞机
I want to let you get on that plane,
但是你必须帮助我们
but you have got to help us out!
你看 我们不得不做我们的工作 好吧？
Look, we have got to do our job here, Okay?
我们必须这样做
We have got to go through this.
在我走之前我需要知道你很冷静且安全
I need to know that you are calm and safe before I leave here.
并且我需要知道你明白所有的规则 然后你才能上飞机
and I need to know that you understand the rules before you get on that plane.
拜托 就
Please, just…
请坐下 让我把这些问题问完
Please, sit down and let us get through our questions.
好吧
Okay.
上帝啊 这是干嘛？
Jesus! What is this?
- 这他妈的是干嘛？- 准备？
- What the hell is this? - Ready?
- 快好了 - 你在干嘛？
- Close. - What are you doing?
放开我
Get off me!
好了吗？
Set?
- 现在放开我 - 准备好了
- Get the hell off me now! - Set!
- 开枪！- 不
- Green! - No!
吉恩
Gene!
我在地下室呢
A runner in the basement!
行动
Go!
- 康妮 - 在你右边
- Connie! - On your right.
抓到她
One. Girl.
找到她
Find her.
Find her!
吉恩 说句话
Gene! Talk to me!
嘿
Hey.
除非你重新上子弹了 枪是空的
Unless you reloaded, the gun is empty.
听着
Look, look.
希林博士 是我
Dr. Shearing, it's me.
- 我不是来伤害你的 - 你怎么
- I'm not here to hurt you, Okay? - How did you…
- 那是你？- 是的 嘘
- That was you! - Yes. Shh!
听我说 你想活命吗？
Listen to me. Do you want to live?
看着我 你想活命吗？
Look at me. Do you want to live?
- 你想活命吗？ - 想
- Do you want to live? - Yes.
很好 放开枪
Good. Let go of this gun.
- 这怎么可能？ - 我们走
- How is this possible? - Let go.
拿着这个
Take this.
很好
Good.
现在你按照我说的做
Now, I need you to do exactly what I say.
- 为什么会这样 - 听我说 按我说的做
- How is this possible? - Listen to me. Exactly what I say.
- 明白？ - 明白
- Understand? - Yeah.
很好
Good.
嘿 博士 我需要我的表
Hey, doc? I need my watch.
我需要我的表
Doc, I need that watch!
房里有摄像头吗？
Are there chems in this house?
实验药物？
Program medication.
他们都死了？
Are they all dead?
是的 都死了
Yeah, they're dead.
看着我 你这儿有计划药物？
Look at me. Look at me. Do you have program medication here?
什么
What?
蓝色的 绿色的药丸 你放在哪儿了？
Chems. Greens, blues. Do you have them here?
- 不 没有 - 没有？
- No, no. - No?
- 这里么？- 不 没有 这里
- Here? No, no. - Here.
那在哪里 你们把药丸放哪了？
Where, then? Where do you have them?
- 哪里？- 你们把药丸放在哪儿？
- Where? - Where do you keep the chems?
我不知道
I don't know.
希林博士 药在哪儿？我要吃药
Dr. Shearing, where are the chems? I need the chems!
我明白 但我不知道在哪儿
I understand, but I don't know.
病毒控制不需要那些东西
It's not something… We do virology control.
所以这一切发生了
So, all of that happens…
我们没有药品
We don't have medication.
如果我有 我肯定会给你
If I had any, I would give it to you.
好吧 听着
Okay, listen to me.
我们只剩不到8分钟从这儿脱身 明白吗？
We have less than eight minutes to clear out of here, Okay?
- 是的 - 很好
- Yes. - Good.
因为下一拨闯进来的人
Because the next thing coming through that door.
会把我们杀光
is going to wipe us out.
能给我讲一下那边的情况么？
Can I get a sitrep, here?
如果听到了 回答我 拉里？
If you can hear me, pick up, Larry.
拉里 回答我
Larry, pick up.
嘿 抱歉
Hey. Sorry about the tran.
计划进展如何？
What's our frame-rate, here?
康妮说还没完 她在做收尾工作
Connie says about 10. Just wrapping up.
有什么需要帮忙的就说
Tell her we need a heads-up. Okay?
知道了
Copy that.
嘿
Hey.
可能还是你来做比较好
It's probably better you did this.
我们要去哪儿？
Where are we going?
琼 你现在叫琼·梦露 说一遍
June. Your name is June Monroe, say it.
- 琼·梦露 - 说一遍
- June Monroe. - Say it.
琼·梦露
June Monroe.
现在 选一个你呆过的地方
Now pick a place you lived.
你最后住的地方 你熟悉的地方
The last place you lived. A place you know.
- 贝塞斯达 - 贝塞斯达 那就是你住的地方
- Bethesda. - Bethesda, that's where you live.
如果有人问起 你就是来自德斯坦的琼·梦露
Anybody asks, you're June Monroe from Bethesda.
你弄丢了钱包 我载你回家
You lost your wallet. I'm driving you home.
我的名字是詹姆斯 詹姆斯和琼 记住了？
My name is James. James and June, you got it?
- 是的 - 很好
- Yeah. - Okay.
那是你的真名么？
Is that your name?
詹姆斯？
James?
不 什么？你难道不知道我名字？
No. What? You don't know my name?
你以前怎么称呼我？你在血液样本上如何做标记？
What do you call me? What do you put on my blood work?
Five.
5？数字5？
Five? The number five?
你知道我们见过多少次？
Do you know how many times we've met?
13次
Thirteen.
过去4年见过13次
Thirteen exams over the last four years.
我就是一个数字？
And that's what I get, a number?
5号？好吧
Number Five. Okay.
多少人中的5号？像我这样的有多少人？
Five of what, then? How many are we?
项目志愿者？
Program participants?
你就这样称呼我们？
That's what you call us?
9人 还剩6人
There were nine. Then six.
志愿者？
Participants.
你是怎么找到我的？
How did you find me?
你认为呢？
Well, what do you think?
他们想要杀掉我们所有人
They're going to kill all of us.
你也别想幸免
and then just leave you guys alone?
你觉得你的同事只是发疯了？
You think your colleague just went crazy?
你就这样认为？
Is that what you think?
- 我 我没有 - 他们把他抓走 又放了
- I didn't think anything. - They wound him up and set him loose.
我真的 真的不知道发生了什么
I really have no idea what is going on.
发生了什么 他们停掉了整个计划
What's going on is they're shutting the whole thing down.
他们是谁？
Who is "they"?
我不 不知道 袭击那所房子的是谁？
I don't know… Who were the people at the house?
- 不 不 - 你已经问过很多问题了 好么？
- No, no, no, no. - You had your turn, Okay?
从我们第一次见 你就不断的给我抽血 问这问那
You've been bleeding and scoping and scraping me since the day we met.
现在轮到我了 该我问你问题 明白吗？
It's my turn, now. I'm asking the questions, you got it?
我需要计划药丸 明白？我需要计划用药
I need program meds, Okay? I need program meds.
你们放在哪里了？
Where do you keep the chems?
我没有 我已经告诉你了
I don't have any. I've already told you.
- 我们没有药 - 胡扯！
- We don't have them. - Bullshit.
- 胡扯！完全是胡扯 - 不 我
- Bullshit. It's bullshit.- No I.
我没有
I don't have any!
你什么都不知道？但是你却在帮忙？
So, you don't know anything? You're just the help?
这就是你住在装了安保系统的大房子里的原因 对吗？
That's why you have the big house and the security clearance, right?
这就是他们要杀你的原因
That's why they're trying so hard to kill you,
因为你什么都不知道？
because you don't know anything.
我知道我的工作是科学研究
I know my job, which is science.
我不知道你们离开实验室做了些什么
I don't know what you do when you leave the lab.
- 我们谁都不知道 - 整整4年
- None of us do! - For four years!
听着 我要下车 求你把车停下
Look, I want to get out! Would you please stop the car?
你不可能那么傻
You can't be that naive.
- 求你让我下车 - 你决不可能那么傻
- Would you let me out the car? - There's no way you're that naive!
你想下车 请便吧 下车
You want out? Get out. Go on, get out.
你没有药丸 不知道它们在哪
You don't have any chems. You don't know where they are.
你什么都不知道 那么很好 滚吧
You don't know anything. That's fine. Just get out.
你已经有个计划了 对吧？
But you got a plan, right?
是啊 你当然有 你是个博士
Yeah, of course you do. You're a doctor.
什么都难不住你 对吗？
You've got this all worked out, don't you?
接下来你要怎么做？
What are you going to do?
嗯？你要怎么做？
Huh? What are you going to do?
你一个人跑不掉 你不知道怎么逃命
You can't run, not alone. You don't know how.
你逃不出他们的手掌心
You certainly can't hide.
他们有的是线索找到你
Not from people like this, with the resources they have.
你逃不过日落你还有什么选择？
You won't make it to sundown. So, what does that leave you?
公之于众？当然 你有发言权
You can go public, sure. You can go loud.
打电话给你妹 因为过去屡试不爽
Call your sister, because that worked out well for you.
打给你前室友？
Call some ex-roommate.
打给某个在华盛顿邮报工作的人
Call a guy that knows a guy at The Washington Post.
放在网上？因为你知道你出卖了我
Put it online. 'Cause you know what?
这就是你能做到唯一计划
You blow me off, that's the only play you've got.
但是你最好先自问一下
But you'd better ask yourself this.
以你发布消息的速度和广度
Could you ever say it loud enough or fast enough.
恐怕还没发布之前就被他们挡下来了吧
that they'd be too afraid to finish what they've started?
现在 我有一个计划 虽然还不完善
Now, I've got a plan, and it's just not that complicated.
我们要做的就是等待下一个杀你的人出现
What I'm going to do is wait for the next person to show up to kill you.
或许他能帮我们
Maybe they can help me.
所以 请便吧
So, go for it.
我没的选择 必须离开那里
I had no choice. I had to get out of there.
不 我必须离开那里
No, I had to get out of there!
不 没人 我不知道
No, nobody. I have no idea.
你要明白 所有计划中的项目成果 那些实验
You have to understand. All the work at Outcome, all those tests,
烧伤恢复率 计量表 器官修复
the burn rates, dosage panels, tissue stress.
那就是我们在做的一一调整配方
I mean, that is us tuning chemistry.
我们并不创造任何东西 都是自然产生的
We don't fabricate anything. That happens downstream.
等等 什么意思？自然产生？
Wait. What's that mean, "downstream"?
就是说你需要活体病毒来引导
It means you need live virus to seed adhesion.
培养过程需要有高度活性
Cultures are highly reactive.
必须现场植入 所以不在实验室做
You have to process on-site and we would never do it here.
好 现场在哪？
Okay. On-site, where? Where?
你说我们把病毒保存在哪？
Where do we hold the virus?
是的
Yes!
呃 开车到不了
Well, we can't drive there.
- 哪里？ - 马尼拉
- Where is it? - Manila.
菲律宾
The Philippines.
你怎么忍受的了那些剂量？
Where do you stand with your dosage?
我还有300毫克蓝药丸
I have 300 milligrams of blues.
不够撑到明天
It's not even enough for another day.
但是我已经超过51小时没服用绿色药丸了
I haven't had a full green in 51 hours,
可是很奇怪 我还没感到体能下降
which is strange because I don't feel physically degraded.
但是 我们想想
But we'll see.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你刚说你还在服用绿色药丸？
Did you just say you're still taking greens?
什么意思？
What are you talking about?
去年你就不需要再吃体能药丸了
You were viraled off physical medication last year.
什么？
What?
天啊 他们8个月前用病毒感染了每个人 不用再吃绿药丸
Jesus. They viraled everyone off greens eight months ago.
用活体病毒感染
They infected you with live virus,
也就是说 身体上已经稳定了
which means that, physically, you're stable.
不用再吃绿药丸
You don't need to take greens.
他们已经稳定了
They locked it in.
任何… 任何身体上的增强都是永久性的
Any physical enhancement is now permanent.
所以 你感染的我？
So, you infected me?
什么时候的事？
When was this?
当我生病的时候？
Is this when I was sick?
那场说不清的流感？是因为你？
The mystery flu? That was you?
呃 不是我 我没有
Well, it wasn't me. I didn't do it.
那就是你 你是故意的 对吗？
That was you. That was on purpose, right?
我差点死了
When I almost died.
我很抱歉 但不是因为我
I'm sorry, but it wasn't me.
那为什么我现在还在吃绿药丸？
Why am I still taking green pills, then?
我不知道 他们 我 我以为你已经停了药
I don't know. I thought you had stopped.
我什么？我为什么还问你
Why am I asking you anything?
是你一直牵制着我们 对吗？
Or to keep us on a leash, right?
是不是？为了控制我们？
Is that it? To keep a hold on us?
为了让我们产生依赖？
To keep us dependent?
谁告诉你这样没有问题？
Who tells you that this is Okay?
不 我做过
No one… I do…
谁说的没问题？
Who says it's Okay?
我做过研究工作
I do research.
设计实验 分析结果 但是我不监管药物
I design, I survey. I don't administer meds.
我不制定政策
I don't make policy!
不 你刚才给枪上了膛
No, you just load the gun.
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
听着 我在那儿做科学研究
Look, I was there for the science.
我们都是做科学研究
We were all there for science.
我知道你不在意 但我作出了巨大的牺牲
And I know you don't care, but I made a huge sacrifice.
我不能公开 不能讨论
I couldn't publish, I couldn't conference.
我不能跟任何人讲我的工作内容
I couldn't tell a single person what it was I did.
但是我以为 我是在帮助我的国家 我知道
But I thought I was helping my country, and I know that's…
告诉我你是不是用病毒
Tell me you can viral off blues.
让我去摆脱蓝药丸的依赖
Can you viral off blues?
理论上讲 可以
Theoretically, yes.
真的？
Yeah.
- 药物只允许暂时性的融合 - 好的
- Pills allow for temporary adhesion.- Okay.
如果要稳定下来 需要活体培养 活体病毒
To lock it in, you need live culture. Live virus!
你知道怎么做？
You know how to do that.
你知道怎么做
Do you know how to do that?
- 是的 - 好的
- Yes. - Okay.
是的 但是我说过了 它们在地球那一边
Yes, but I told you, it's on the other side of the planet.
我知道我们要去哪了
Well, guess where we're going?
欢迎来到华盛顿 欢迎来到启明世贸大厦
Welcome to Washington. Welcome to Candent World Headquarters.
我们要确认在接下来的几天里
We want to make sure that over the next few days.
你们都有机会接触到造就斯特森·莫兰塔的人们
you have a chance to connect with the people who have made Sterisyn Morlanta.
他们都是启明集团公司的精英
the crown jewel in the Candent group of companies.
这个月第三阶段的测试将得到批准
Final Phase 3 testing approval is expected this month.
包括镇静剂和抑制剂
for both reQuiel and Supressolyn.
我们很有信心 如期实现目标
Confidence is high that we're coming in on schedule, and we want to be ready.
我们知道市场
We know the market is eager.
我们也知道全球化 和
We know, globally, the kind of…
见鬼为什么我不知道这些？
What the hell don't I know about this?
你在指控我？
You're directing that at me?
我们派了一支D队过去
That was a D-Trac team we sent in there.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what that means.
就是说他们是这方面的佼佼者
It means they're good at what they do.
但我听说他们都失踪了
I was told that they were missing.
不仅仅是失踪
They don't just go missing.
为什么不给我们讲讲这个女人？
What didn't you tell us about this woman?
没什么好讲的 她就是她而已
Nothing. She is who she is. There's nothing to tell.
要她怎样就怎样
You vetted her up and down.
那我们究竟知道什么？
Then what the hell are we looking at?
她有把注册的枪
She has a registered gun.
他们要行动
They knew that going in.
她有通行证
She's got building permits.
丙烷 焊接罐 流弹
Propane, welding tanks. A stray bullet?
你还继续猜下去？
You want to keep guessing?
我们要过去看看
We've got to get in there.
周围有12人待命
I've got a dozen people waiting on the perimeter.
我们还没控制现场？
We don't control the site?
暂时没有
Not yet.
现在了解情况了？
Getting the picture now?
别说了
Okay, stop!
在这里我没法处理
I can't run this from here.
我要进行全面搜查 我要所有相关团队和通讯设施
I need a crisis suite. I need integrated grids and comms.
全都要
I need all of it.
宇航局 五角大楼或者自由女神像
NSA, or Pentagon, or Liberty Crossing.
我不管是什么 都要
I don't care, just get me something now.
穿上衣服 开上车
Pack up your codes and your drives,
快点准备就绪
and whatever else you're going to need.
我们要马上行动 守在那儿
We're going to move and we're going to stay there.
对那所房子彻底布控 周围都是当地平民
Dita, how am I putting a net over that house? There's locals all over it.
我们来查病毒
We go with germs.
她把实验室中的样本带走了
She took samples from work.
病原体 病毒 这可是国土安全问题
Pathogens, viruses. It's national security.
好 低调行事
Good, Okay, I like that, it plays.
快行动去吧 快行动去吧
Now, get it out there, get it out there.
快 每个人再拿一样东西
Come on, let's go, let's go. Everybody find another gear, Okay?
我要你们20秒内离开
Because I want to be out of here in 20.
就是说你想改变人体
So, let's say you want to change the human body.
修复错误
You want to fix a mistake.
你想弥补什么 增强什么
You want to repair something, improve something.
如果你将人类基因进行重组
Well, if you're going to reprogram human genetic material,
你需要一个传送系统 病毒最好不过
you need a delivery system, and nothing works better than virus.
有点像旅行箱
It's like a suitcase.
你把基因打包
You pack in genetic mutation,
感染人体 病毒会将之输送到目标细胞中
infect the body and the vector unloads into the target cells.
但是如何到达你想要的地方 怎么做到
But getting it where you want it, how you want it,
简直就是噩梦
is the nightmare.
除非你有张图谱
Unless you have a map.
1985年德特里克堡发生过一起严重事故
There was this terrible accident at Fort Detrick in 1985.
5名研究员在实验室中死亡 就是因此产生的灾难
Five researchers dropped dead in the lab, and it was such a catastrophe.
他们从斯坦福把丹·希尔科
that they brought in Dan Hillcott.
调了过去评估损失情况
from Stanford to assess the damage.
然后他到了那儿意识到 这件事使他在
He got in there and he realized that, underneath it all,
病毒受体图谱绘制方面有了重大突破
was this incredible breakthrough in viral-receptor mapping.
他绘制了图谱
He had a map.
你身上有一些不同染色体的细微改变
You've had some very minor alterations.
made to two different chromosomes.
绿色部分 身体部分
The green side, the physical side,
就是1.5%的
is nothing more than a 1.5 percent rise.
你的线粒体蛋白含量
in your mitochondrial protein uptake.
不过增加了1.5%
But with 1.5 percent,
让你的细胞分裂速度
you see this immediate increase in cellular tempo,
肌肉韧性和氧合作用大幅增加
muscle efficiency, oxygenation…
在蓝色部分？
And the blue side?
智力 很明显 但不至于次
Intelligence, obviously, but it's more than that.
神经再生 敏捷度
It's neural regeneration and elasticity.
感应功能 痛苦抑制
Sensory function. Pain suppression.
这是令人兴奋的进步
It's the most exciting development in genomic targeting.
在科学史上的染色体标记方面
in the history of the science.
天啊
My God.
嘿 怎么把71号监控器显示在大屏幕上？
Hey, how do I get monitor 71 up on the big screen?
过来
Coming up.
他们发现一具尸体
They found a body.
确认是女性 但肯定不是玛塔·希林
They're pretty sure it's a woman, and it's not Marta Shearing.
他们发现了身份牌子
They found dog tags.
他们认为他被枪杀了
They think she was shot.
嘿
Hey.
你好
玛塔 我
Marta, I…
你不能打给任何人
You can't call anyone.
他们都是关心你 认为你已经死了的人
There are people that care about you that think you're dead.
对此你无能为力
And there's nothing you can do about it.
你联系的任何人都会成为目标
Anyone you contact becomes a target.
所以你要放得下任何正常的情感
So, you need to put aside any normal emotional response that you have.
我们现在最大的优势 就是他们认为我们都死了
The only edge we've got right now is they think we're both gone.
明白？
All right?
好吧
All right.
那么
So,
如果你实在是放不下
you're going to want to go through this.
多熟悉熟悉它
You know, just be familiar with it.
琼·梦露
June Monroe.
谁是琼·梦露？
Who is June Monroe?
你就是
You are.
你认识她？
Do you know her?
曾经
Not any more.
为什么你要让自己强大起来？
Why do you have to stay enhanced?
为什么这对你如此重要？
Why is it so important to you?
过来
Come here.
（陨落的英雄 纪念那些死去的人）
这是什么？
What is this?
这是曾经的我
This was me.
曾经是
Was.
我的应征官
My army recruiter.
他为了完成分配的任务
was looking to make his quota.
给我的智商多加了12点
He added 12 points to my IQ.
加12分才达到最低标准线
Twelve points to make the minimum.
你见过智力低下的人吗 玛塔
You ever seen a cognitive degrade, Marta?
反应迟钝的呢 见过吗
Sensory withdrawal? You ever do that?
将蓝色的药停掉看他们的反应
Pull someone's blues and watch them drop off their meds?
没
No.
就像是描绘一幅美丽的梦中图画
Because they paint a pretty graphic picture in training.
和现实有落差
Hell of a long way to fall.
要是你不打起精神 我们熬不过去
If I can't keep it together, we won't make it.
- 他们做了这些 - 谁？
- They bit. - Who?
华盛顿邮报
Washington Post.
刚刚截获的邮件
We just flagged an email.
他们略有耳闻
They're going with the story about the possible theft.
实验危险物质遭窃事件
of the dangerous materials from the lab.
还真信了 他们已经认定是酒驾
Wow, they took it. They already flagged a DWI conviction.
这下更省事了
That's convenient.
我们发现了另一具尸体 我们的人
They found another body. One of ours.
他们在那儿回收一地的子弹壳
They're picking up shell casings all over the place.
我认为你的博士已经不在那儿了
I don't think your doctor's in there.
请出示身份证和登机证
Boarding pass and ID, please.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
请出示身份证和登机证
Boarding pass and ID, please.
你在哪儿
Where are you?
就在你身后 别转身
I'm right behind you. Don't turn around.
你就呆在这儿
You're going to stay right here.
直到登机 好吗？你做的很好
until it's time to board, Okay? You're doing great.
看到你右边的通道了？
You see that corridor on your right?
发现有人走那边
You're gonna want to find somebody.
跟着那人走就是了
who's walking that way and just tag along.
一直走 低着头
Keep moving, keep your head down,
飞机上见
and I'll see you on the plane.
亚伦
Aaron?
喂？
Hello?
痕迹很清晰 刚留下的
The trail is definitive and fresh.
警犬从她家追踪到她
The canine team tracked her from her house.
穿过这片林地 然后是这儿 在这个停车场
through this wooded area, ending here, at this little parking lot.
要么是她在那边有辆车 要么就是有人开车接应她
Either she had a car waiting for her, or somebody picked her up.
街上的监控显示那儿什么都没有
There are security cameras on the street, but there's nothing back here.
肯定有卫星监控图
There's got to be satellite footage.
马里兰州不是美国的高危进攻目标
Maryland's not exactly a high-value U.S. target.
我们有不少卫星云图
There'll be plenty of weather imaging,
我们只能看个大概
but we're gonna have to swing a little wider.
不能看实时画面
to find something real-time that's enhanceable.
我们需要筛选一些国外监控 这差不多要一小时
We're draining some foreign platforms. We need about an hour.
不是吧 她一个人怎么能做的这么缜密
Come on, she's not pulling this off on her own.
谁在帮她呢？
Who the hell is helping her?
我们要找到要在1小时外
We'll find out more in the next hour,
会发现 我们目前当然在
while we are currently in court.
回来 Jen
Now back to Jenn.
FBI今早已证实阿尔伯特·赫希博士
The FBI this morning confirmed reports that Dr. Albert Hirsch.
在华盛顿一家旅馆里死于心脏病
died of heart failure in a Washington, D. C. hotel.
赫希博士有望在昨天
Dr. Hirsch had been expected to testify yesterday.
向特工委员会做证实报告
before a Senate Intelligence committee.
委员会正在调查
That select committee is investigating links.
CIA问题频出的绊脚石计划
between a troubled CIA program known as Treadstone.
是否与杰森·伯恩此人相关
and this man, Jason Bourne.
警察和联邦人员正在调查
Police and federal officials are searching for Bourne.
此案是否与近期纽约和伦敦发生的枪击案有关
in connection with recent shootings in New York and in London.
赫希博士一直希望与司法部门进行合作
Dr. Hirsch had been cooperating with the Justice Department.
悲剧发生时他正处在证人保护监控中
and was in protective custody at the time of the incident.
昨晚一名委员会发言人告诉记者
A committee spokesman told reporters last night.
听证会暂时推迟
that the hearings will be postponed temporarily.
因为正在调查博士的死亡
as they evaluate the loss of Doctor…
（研究员混乱的过去让实验室调查疑云重重）
嗨 伙计们
Hi, folks.
只是提醒你们 保持这里的过道通畅
Just going to remind you to keep the aisles clear.
在起飞和着陆时
for any baggage during takeoff and landing.
- 借过 - 谢谢
- Excuse me. - Thank you.
借过 先生
Pardon me, sir.
先生 要帮您找座位吗？
Sir, do you need help finding your seat?
- 先生 - 不用了
- Sir? - No, I got it.
看到那两个阴影了？其中一个是她 那就是停车场
You see those two shadows? One of them is her. That's the parking lot.
其中一个停下了 车来了
One of them stops. Here comes the car.
- 这录像哪来的？ - 加拿大森林卫星
- Where is this from? - It's a Canadian forestry satellite.
好 然后另一个人上了车 在这儿 然后他们走了
Here comes the other one into the car, and there they go.
- 哪里？- 我们跟丢了他们
- Where? - We lose them east.
公路以外2公里无法监控了
Our window drops out about two miles up the road.
但我们有个大致轮廓
But we've got the silhouette.
我们有道路监控录像 可以马上看
We've got surveillance footage, racked and ready to go.
我们分组查找这辆车 绘制他们的行动轨迹
We're going to split teams, find this car and link up atrail.
要持续17小时？
With a 17-hour head start?
她还能跑到哪儿去？
Where the hell can she go?
我们在找一辆新的别克LeSabre 2000型
We're looking for a Buick LeSabre 2002.
我有国家情报局和国家安全局的搜查令 这就是原因
I've got an NIA/Homeland warrant, that's why.
- 你能给我你们那儿的信息么？- 2位乘客
- Well, you give us what you have… - Two passengers.
是一辆02年产的紫红色LeSabre 从马里兰州里斯本向西行驶
It's an '02 burgundy LeSabre starting west from Lisbon, Maryland.
便利店 服务站 加油站
Tolls, exits, service stations.
给我所有你有的监控录像
Give me every camera you've got.
这边能看到FBI的监控影像
I'm seeing an FBI camera bin on my list here.
不 不 只要交通的
No, no. Traffic only.
里斯本 L-I-S-B-O-N
West, Lisbon. L-I-S-B-O-N.
是的 我们都要 所有监控录像 什么都要
Yes, we want all of that and the toll cams. We want everything.
我们全要 不管你们有什么 都传送过来
We'll take them all. Whatever hits you have, send them on.
我们会做分类处理
We will work on sorting them out.
在威尔明顿 特拉华州发现
Wilmington, Delaware.
这就是我们要的车 这辆LeSabre 它向这个建筑驶来
This is our car, the LeSabre. We see it coming into the structure.
向下开 转个弯 在这里面停车
It goes under, comes back around, and it parks here.
然后就没出来过
But it doesn't come out.
这是车进去前4分钟的内部影像
This is inside. It's four minutes after arrival.
就是她
It's her.
我们知不知道她要做什么？
Do we know what she's doing?
她在拍护照照片
She was having her passport picture taken.
（菲律宾 马尼拉）
洛根 哈特福德 拉瓜迪亚 肯尼迪 费城 纽华克机场
Logan, Hartford, LaGuardia, Kennedy, Philly, Newark,
杜勒斯机场 里根机场
Dulles, Reagan.
我们开始发布通缉警告 那就是我们要找的人
We start with yesterday morning, that is our wedge.
说清楚 然后按计划行事
We clear that, and then we move up the clock.
她问要不要哈特福德机场的 她可以拿到记录
She wants to know if you want Hartford, because she can get it.
蓝外套 第二排 她带了个红色的包
Blue coat, second row. She's got a red bag.
哪一个 我有4个
Which one? I have four.
我有4个运输安全局授权授权1 6 9 12号
All right, I have TSA Authorization 1, 6, 9 and 12.
以上机场 所有部门
Airports given, all departures.
是的 首先查国际航班
Yes, the international terminal first.
我们马上到啦
We're almost there.
检查一下报亭
So, check out the newsstand.
这里
There.
呃 我不知道
I don't know.
洛根机场有一张面孔你应该看看
Logan has a face we need to look at, but there's kids.
停下 停下 停下
Hang on, hang on, hang on. Hang on.
停
Stop.
哪儿？
Where is this?
- 肯尼迪机场 - 好的
- Kennedy. - Okay.
我从未在晚上来过 不知道有什么规矩
I've never been here at night. I don't know the rules.
没什么规矩 好吗？
There are no rules, Okay?
你属于这儿 来
We belong here. Come on.
嘿 你好吗？
Hey, how are you?
晚上好
Good evening.
希林博士和我来这儿 请打开实验室大门
Dr. Shearing and I are here to open up the lab, please.
- 长官 - 怎么回事
- Sir? - What's all this?
嗨 你好吗？
Hi, how are you?
希林博士 希林博士
Dr. Shearing! Dr. Shearing.
是我 约瑟夫
Hey, it's me, Joseph.
约瑟夫
Joseph!
你好 近来如何？
Hello, how are you?
我很好
I'm good, I'm good.
- 欢迎回来 - 谢谢
- Welcome back. - Thanks.
不好意思 接待名单上没有你
I'm sorry. I just don't have you on my list arriving.
因为我们改了日程
That's because we had to change our schedule.
我们坐了早一班的飞机
Yeah, we took an earlier flight.
约瑟夫 我是布伦戴奇医生 见到你很高兴
Joseph, I'm Dr. Brundage, by the way. It's nice to meet you.
见到你也很高兴 但是可普马洛医生不在这儿 他去了新加坡
Pleased to meet you, too, but Dr. Pumaloy is not here, he went to Singapore.
昨天刚走
He just left yesterday.
我以为您回家了 没人告诉我您会来
The girls have gone home. No one told me anything.
没关系 嗯 我懂
Right. Well, I understand.
我们要在这儿呆一周
Well, look, we're going to be here all week,
有很多事情要做
and we have a lot of work to do,
所以每晚都会来
so we need to get in there tonight.
所以赶快开始吧 好吗？
and get things started, Okay?
是 当然 但是
Yeah, of course, it's just that…
如果你愿意你可以打电话给可普马洛博士
You can call Dr. Pumaloy if you want.
我可没逼你这么做
I just don't want to put you on the spot.
不 不用
No, we don't have to do that.
那很好
Okay, great.
只是你们俩？
It's just the two of you?
是的
Yeah.
是 没错
Yes, correct.
没错
Correct.
是 我等着
Yes, I will hold.
把那个放到大屏幕上
Get it up there. Put that up on the big screen.
是的 我还在
Yes, I'm here.
好 哪里？
Good. Where?
我需要一份旅客名单
I need an immediate upload on that passenger manifest.
我知道她在名单上 我会让她接电话
I know. Here she is, I'm putting her back on.
马尼拉
Manila.
她乘美国167号航班去马尼拉了
She took American 167 to Manila.
45分钟前着陆
She landed 45 minutes ago.
亚伦
Aaron.
你还好？
Are you Okay?
有243名乘客在那次航班上
There's 243 people on that plane.
我们要立刻辨认每个人
We're going to scope every one of them right now.
如果发现任何一张熟悉的脸 点击出来
So, pick a face that you like, pull it down,
真的没问题再关闭
and deselect it if you've cleared it.
若有任何你觉得不对劲的地方
If there is anything that smells wrong to you,
即使是蛛丝马迹
if there's a hair out of place that you don't like,
不要放过
you do not clear it.
做上标记 发过来 我们会做辨认
You flag it and you send it over to Dita and we'll check it out.
我们要对同样的网格进行筛选 就是国土安全9 5
We have to be working off the same grid. That's Homeland 9.5.
如果你们没有访问权 请举手
If you don't pull that access, raise your hand,
哈迪上校会帮你解决
Colonel Hardy's going to come over and sort you out.
就是这儿？
So, this is it, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我们究竟在查什么 特里？
What the hell are we into, Terry?
我不知道
I don't know.
那是你的工厂 你们在那儿做什么？
It's your shop. What is going on over there?
没听到我说的吗？我不知道
What did I say? I don't know.
她一共去过那里几次？
Well, how many trips has she made over there?
5 6次 我不清楚 为什么是菲律宾？
Five, six, I don't know. Why the Philippines?
嗨
Hey, hey, hey!
座位13B 卡尔·T·布伦戴奇 13B
Seat 13-B. Karl D. Brundage, 13-B.
都有协助人员都离开房间
I need support staff to clear the room.
站起来都出去 马上
Stand up and walk, now.
回去 快 我们走
Jack, Cathy, move! Let's go.
他究竟是谁？
Who the hell is he?
他是成果计划的特工人员
He's an Outcome agent.
特工5号
That's Outcome 5.
他还没死？我以为他们都死光了
They're not dead? I thought they were dead!
是 他本应该已经死了
Yeah, he's supposed to be dead.
- 那他在那儿做什么？- 我不知道
- Then what's he doing there? - I don't know.
他在找药丸
He's looking for meds.
什么？
What?
药品都是那里生产的 不然他去那儿做什么
That's where the chems come from. What else would he be doing?
她一定是在帮他
She's got to be helping him.
怎么去的？怎么可能？
But how? How is that possible?
我不知道 也不在乎
I don't know how. I don't care.
他还活着 他们在那
He's alive, they're there.
怎么已经无关紧要了 对吧？
"How" doesn't really matter, does it?
我们现在唯一的任务 就是要彻底干掉他们
The only mission we've got now is to drop a bag over this.
他要找的药丸不在那儿？
Are the drugs he's looking for there, or not?
天啊 我必须 特里？
Jesus, I don't… Terry?
不不 那儿什么都没有
No. No, there's nothing there.
政府已经接管了16周
We haven't made a run in 16 weeks.
而且我们也不可能保存什么药品
Besides, we wouldn't store the pills there, anyway.
那里基本上就是个加工厂
It's basically a kitchen.
我们提供药方 在需要的时候加工生产一下
We tweak the recipe and we bake up a batch when we need it.
那他们去那儿做什么？
Then what the hell are they doing?
病毒在那儿？
The stems are there.
她一定是帮他用病毒治病
She's going to try to viral him out.
谢谢
Thank you.
马克？
Mack. Yeah?
车间办公室 我是马克
Plant office, Mackie speaking.
马克 我是特伦斯·沃德
Mr. Mackie, this is Terrance Ward.
我是启明集团的副主席
I'm the Senior Vice-President for Candent Precision Metrics.
- 这是从马里兰打来的电话 是的 - 先生
- I'm calling from Maryland. - Yes, sir.
我们有一个潜在的安全威胁
We have a potential security incident.
我在公司网站上发布了两张照片
I just posted two photographs on the company network.
我想知道是不是这两人试着闯进
I need to know if either of these two people have tried to enter…
是 我们在调查
Yeah, we're on it.
说什么？
Excuse me?
我们正在查 我们正在想应该给谁打电话
Yeah, we're on the case. We're just here now trying to figure out who to call.
我们的门卫接待了两位医生
Our gatehouse just passed in two doctors.
我想其中一人自称希林博士
I think one of them might be that woman.
枪击案中的女博士
from your shoot-out over there.
他们现在在哪儿？
Well, where are they now?
我们所有的重要实验室都在楼下
We keep all of our client labs downstairs,
所以我认为他们去了地下室
so we're assuming they've gone into the basement.
我刚派了人去查
I just sent a couple of boys down to check it out.
不不不 把你的人撤回来
No, no. No, no, withdraw your team.
锁上地下室 把他们关在下面
Lock the lab and keep them down there.
别试着抓他们
Do not try to take him.
你好
Hello?
嘿 你干什么呢？需要帮助吗？
Hey, how you doing? Can I help you?
你们单独在这儿？
Are you alone down here?
亚伦
Aaron?
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
你们不能到这里来 你们有这个等级授权吗？
You can't be down here. Do you have clearance for this level?
任何人都不该到下面来
Nobody's supposed to be down here.
我可以到这里来 我是希林博士
I'm supposed to be down here. I'm Dr. Shearing.
我们正在做采样
We're in the middle of a sampling audit.
你们在这里不安全
It is not safe for you guys to be here.
请跟我们上楼
Let's straighten this out upstairs.
- 别碰我 - 收拾好 我们上去
- Don't touch that. - Pack it up, let's go.
- 听着 别碰那个 - 跟我们上楼
- Look, nobody touch anything. - Come on, just follow us.
我不想跟你们争吵 我要给你们老板打电话
I'm not going to sit here and argue with you. I'm going to call your boss.
- 我们会消除误会的 - 看着她
- and we're gonna figure it out.- Watch her.
嘿 等一下
Hey, hold on a second.
我去拿包 我们走
I'm going to get my bag. We got to go.
好
Okay.
不 这边
Wait. This way.
- 我不知道这通向哪里 - 开开就行了
- I don't know where this goes. - Just open it.
往后站
Step back.
关门 嘿 说你呢 快点
Lock it down. Hey! You! You! With me! Come on, come on, come on.
- 这儿关了么？ - 是 长官
- Is that locked? - Yes, sir.
不许有人进出 懂吗？
No one in, no one out. Do you understand?
嘿 我们在严格监控下 你待在楼下
Hey, what happened to those three guys you sent downstairs?
妈的
Shit.
我们去看看 你呆着别走 明白？
Come with me. You stay there, Okay? Stay there.
你是属于这里的
We belong here.
过去
Coming through.
你 去把其他人喊来 告诉他们到门口去
You, go and get everyone else. Tell them to go around the front.
去东门 然后绕到前门
Go through the eastern doors, move around the front.
快点 快点 大家
Move! Move, people!
这个无线电是谁的 怎么没人回答
Who have you got on this radio? Why is no one responding?
门关了吗
Is that gate shut?
抱歉 快 快 快
Excuse me. Move, move, move!
我得关上门
Hey! I need that gate shut!
嘿 你 听着 去正门 明白吗
Hey, you! Listen, go down to the main gate. Do you understand?
不许有人进出
No one in, no one out.
嘿 你在干啥？
Hey, what are you doing?
和其他人一样排队
Just get down to the main gate with everyone else.
后退 后退 让一让
All right, get back! Stay back!
给他点空间
Give him some room.
好 让一让 让一让
All right, give me some room. Give me some room, please.
好 他需要看医生
He's going to need a doctor.
保安？保安
Security. Security!
请到这边来
Over here, please.
让开
Over here.
先生 你能听到我说话？
Sir, can you hear me? Sir!
他跑不远的
He can't get far.
如果他不能用病毒治疗 他肯定坚持不住
If he didn't viral out, he's going to run out of brain.
如果他用病毒治疗 会变得太虚弱走不动路
And, if he did, then he's going to be too sick to move.
所以我们只要尽快找到他
So, we just have to find him fast.
杀了他了事
and kill him, once and for all.
现在可以提拉斯计划了吗？
Can we talk about LARX?
拉斯计划？
LARX?
拉斯3号在曼谷 大概2小时航程
LARX-3 is in Bangkok. It's atwo-hour flight.
等一下 先等等
Wait a minute. Just hang on, here.
我以为那只是个提议
I thought that was just a proposal.
派他过去
Get him out there.
拉斯是增强版备用计划
LARX is a beta-Z stem program.
绝对忠诚于任务 冷血无情
Amped mission fidelity, minimized empathy.
他是比绊脚石计划更稳定
It's Treadstone without the inconsistency,
比成果计划更没有情感漏洞的人
Outcome without the emotional noise.
他看起来非常强壮
It's looking very strong for us.
我们从未见过像这样的
We have never seen evaluations like this.
这个计划我不知情
This went from something I don't know about.
只是纸上谈兵的计划
to something on the drawing board,
现在你却告诉我它正良好运行？
and now you're telling me it's up and running?
确实在良好运行 现在你已经知道了
It's up and running. Consider yourself informed.
你还好吗？
Are you comfortable?
是的
Yes, sir.
你看起来不太舒服
You don't look comfortable.
不
No, sir.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
肯尼斯·詹姆斯
Kenneth James.
全名 肯尼斯
Full name, Kenneth.
詹姆斯
Kenneth… James…
凯特森
Kitsom.
他们有房间
They have a room.
你能走路吗？
Can you walk?
可以 可以 我想可以的
Yeah? Yeah. Yeah. I think so.
你从哪儿来？肯尼斯
Where are you from, Kenneth?
什么时间？
When?
在你报名之前
Before you enlisted.
伯温
Berwin.
那是座城镇么？
Is that a town?
是个州的首府
Berwin… It's a state home.
哪个州？
What state?
里诺州
In Reno.
这是个测试？
Is this a test?
是的
Yes, it is.
如果我通过了就能留下来？
If I pass, can I stay here?
你想留下？
Do you want to stay?
是的
Yes, sir.
那样就好
That's good to know.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
好 呆着别动
Okay, just lie still.
艾伦 你得 艾伦
Aaron, you have… Aaron…
什么？
What?
有四万美元 在我夹克衬里里面
There's $40, 000 in the lining of my jacket.
这个包里有护照
In this bag, there are passports.
两个空白的 三张假身份 还有个手表
Two blanks and three ghosts, there's that guy's watch.
还有些其他的东西 ？你拿着
There are other things, Okay? You take it.
看着我
Look at me.
你能熬过去的
You can make it.
你是个战士
You're a warrior.
你能熬过去的
You can make it.
低调行事
Okay? Stay small.
不要坐飞机
No airports.
融入人群里消失 你懂的
Just blend in like you know, Okay?
你为我做的已经够多了
You've done enough for me.
不 我
No, I…
你离开吧
Please go.
你已经为我做的够多了
You've done enough for me.
一切都在车里
Everything's in the car.
这是个测试？
Is this a test?
是的
Yes, it is.
如果我通过了就能留下？
If I pass, can I stay here?
你想留下吗？
Do you want to stay?
（出去买药了）
扑热息痛 500mg
Paracetamol, 500 milligrams.
一天四次
Four times a day.
免费的 这是免费的
For free. This is free.
好的
Okay, good.
我会回来的
I'll be right back.
亚伦 快跑
Aaron, run!
你在哪？
"Where are you?"
那是信号吗？
"Was that the signal?"
他们请求确认
They're asking for confirmation.
你们去太早了 不 我们去太早了
"You went too soon." No… "We went too soon."
快点
Come on.
没事
It's Okay.
警察 警察
Police! Police!
蹲下
Get down!
你没事吧？
Are you Okay?
是的
Yeah.
很好 快走
Good. Come on.
蹲下
Get down, get down.
快 爬上去
Climb over.
快 爬过去 爬过去
Go. Get over, get over, get over.
爬过去 抓紧
Get over. Hang on tight.
快 快
Go, go!
准备好了？松手
You ready? Let go!
好 拿上这个
Okay. Take this.
继续走 别回头 走
Just keep walking, don't look back. Go, go.
嘿 嘿上车
Hey, hey. Get on.
- 你从没骑过这个？ - 没
- You ever ridden before? - No.
拿着
Take this.
警察 警察
Police, police!
抓紧 抓着我 好
Hang on tight and follow me, Okay?
抓紧
Stay with me.
他有把枪
He's got a gun!
低头
Keep your head down.
他不是警察
It's not a cop.
亚伦
Aaron!
- 你中枪了？- 没事
- You've been shot. - It's all right.
停车
Pull over!
Pull over.
得去找点水
We just have to get to the water.
帮我查一下
Can you check that for me?
要多长时间？
How long is that going to take?
快点
Come on.
我们会回复你
We'll get back to you.
有进展？
Anything?
没
No.
警察们都被甩掉了
The cops are out.
他们跟丢了
They lost the trail.
亚伦
Aaron!
亚伦 亚伦 亚伦
Aaron! Aaron! Aaron! Aaron!
你没事吧？
Are you Okay?
没事
Yeah? Yeah.
能帮帮我们吗？
Can you help us?
求你了
Please.
现在应该有消息了
Should be up there now.
这是他们过夜的房间
He said it's the room where they spent the night.
（到此为止）
六年前我们的绊脚石计划出现了问题
Well, we had a problem with Treadstone six years ago.
黑石楠计划也是
The Blackbriar program,
你面前的就是这些行动的详细计划
detailed in the operations report you have before you,
启动这个计划仅仅是为了
was activated solely to capture.
逮捕一个失控的绊脚石计划
a Treadstone operative gone rogue.
帕姆 你会怎么做
Pam, what are you going to do?
无可奉告
We have nothing for you now.
我不知道帕梅拉·兰迪为什么会
I don't know Pamela Landy's reasons.
反法律 帮助与国家为敌的人
for criminally assisting an enemy of the United States.
但事实是 她没有行动权限
But the fact is, she lacked the operational clearance.
更不用说接触到
to access, much less interpret, the information you have.
这些摆在你们面前的机密文件
in the classified file before you.
帕姆 有传言说你被起诉 这真的吗
Pam, there's a rumor that you're going to be indicted, is it true?
- 马克 对此有何评论？- 你收到传讯了吗
- Mike, can you comment? - Have you been subpoenaed?
我们是自愿来的 我们来参与会议的
We're here voluntarily. We came for a meeting.
你是否还在与杰森·伯恩吗？
Have you had any contact with Jason Bourne?
你收到法院传单了吗？
Did you receive a target letter or not?
我们要看到明天吗？
Are we going to see you tomorrow?
感谢上帝 她翅膀还不是太硬
I just thank God that there were hands steady enough.
在造成进一步不良影响之前
to make sure that the documents she tried to shop to the press.
要确保这些她即将公布给媒体
were contained before they could.
的文件被严格控制住
do any more harm than they already have.
你还会如期出现在众议会特勤委员会么？
Are you still scheduled to appear at the House Intelligence Committee?
是的 其他事情找我律师谈 好吗？
Yes, I am. Look, anything else is going to have to come from my attorneys, Okay?
你对之前的陈述后悔吗？
Do you regret your earlier statement?
我对很多事情后悔 但这件不
I regret a lot of things. I'm not sure that one is on the list.
谢谢大家
Thank you, guys.
嘿
Hey.
我们迷路了吗？
Are we lost?
没有
No.
我看看还有什么选择
Just looking at our options.
我倒是希望我们迷路了
I was kind of hoping we were lost.